

- 1393, New Gouri Nagar, Indore
- sjkajal98@gmail.com
- 9826755997

SKILLS SUMMARY

- Angular
- Node.js
- React.js
- SQL
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap
- Mongodb
- AWS
- Azure

SOFTWARES SUMMARY

- Postman
- WinSCP
- Mongodb Compass,
- SqlYog, phpMyAdmin
- MS SQL management
- NoSql Booster, Studio 3T
- Visual Studio Code
- Sublime
- Gitlab
- GitHub, bitbucket
- Jira

DEPLOYMENT

- AWS Instance
- Azure app service
- Azure virtual machine
- SSL certificate
- Private and public key

ACHIEVEMENT

- Client-side visit to Singapore for 7 days.
- E-Leader of M-tycoon's E-cell(MIST) running by NEN,
 India
- Representative of college in NEN E-Leader workshop.
- 1st Prize in Innovative Poster making competition.

KAJAL SINGHAI

FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

Full stack Developer with 2.10 years of experience as developer and 3 months of experience as intern. Successfully developed and maintained applications using advanced technologies such as React.js, Angular, NodeJS with express, REST, MicroServices Architecture, TypeScript and MySQL, Mongodb, Azure Databases.

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Bachelor of Engineering in Computer Science- 8.0 CGPA

Malwa Institute of Science and Technology, Indore | 2016-2020

HSC-60%

St. Vincent Pallotti School, Indore | CBSE board | 2015 - 2016

SSC-8.0 CGPA

St. Vincent Pallotti School, Indore | CBSE board | 2013 - 2014

WORK EXPERIENCE

Software Developer

Mindcrew Technologies | Oct 2020 - present

MERN-Stack projects

- Food delivery application
- Electronic Medical Record- Patient management.
- Monitive Health Track the visits and calculate, predict the revenue generated from each patient in a hospital.
- Client connect Provide leads of criminals to lawyers.

MEAN-Stack projects

- Sage aadmin- Keeps records of all rides of drivers.
- CBT- Clinic management system.

Node.js projects

- Fx-buddy Foreign currency exchange machine.
- Pingahla Create connection between two systems.

Integrations

- Singpass which authentic the Singapore citizens.
- Worked on Azure App-service and Azure Virtual machine.
- Sendgrid for sending routine e-mail to users.
- MailChimp for creating seperate contacts and email marketing for each user of application.
- Stripe payment gateway for recurring subscriptions.
- Hitpay for the payment through QR code of Paynow.
- Integrated current foreign exchange rates API for SGD.
- Google login and Facebook login.

Node is Developer

Ideavate Solutions | Jan 2020 - April 2020

Worked on Employment management system.

Internship

Torenia Technologies | Jan 2019 - April 2019

- Used node.js, HTML, bootstrap to work on insurance registration application and its admin panel in.
- Used node.js, HTML, bootstrap work on social media application with the feature like post, create friends and create room.